International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Local 686 (Lockport, NY) Records 5677
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Local 686 (Lockport, NY) Records
1940-1962
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Local 686 (Lockport, NY)
5677
11 cubic feet
11 linear ft.
Articles, rep0rts, pamphlets, correspondence.
3121930
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 18, 2005
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, June 24, 2013
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5677 mf: International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Local 686 (Lockport, NY). Records, 1940-1977. Microfilm. 5677 AV: International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Local 686 (Lockport, NY) Audio-Visual Material
3121930
- The Distributor, 1941-1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Defense Employment, 1941-1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Club 686 (Box 1, Folder 16-18)
- C.I.O. War Relief (Box 1, Folder 15)
- City Council (Box 1, Folder 14)
- City Clerk (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Bulletin Board Notices (Box 1, Folder 11-12)
- Board of Education (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Board of Education (Box 1, Folder 9)
- American Labor Party, 1944-1948 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Affiliates correspondence, 1944-1948 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Agreement, Harrison Radiator, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Addes, George, 1940-1945 (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
- General Correspondence and Papers (Box 1, Folder 0)
- News - U.A.W. Press, 1944-1946 (Box 2, Folder 18-19)
- Murray, Philip, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Members' letters (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Mazey, E., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Lockport Industrial Union Council, C.I.O. (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Loans (Credit Union) (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Lake, Kenneth, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Housing Committee (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Gray, Edward, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Gerber, Martin, 1944-1946 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- General Motors (Box 2, Folder 5-8)
- Garno, Harold J., 1944-1946 (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
- Frankensteen, Richard, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Education Committee (Box 2, Folder 1)
- War Labor Board (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Thomas, R.J., 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Stewards (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Smith Connally Act (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Reuther, Walter, 1944-1948 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Reuther, Walter, 1944-1948 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Reuther, Walter, 1944-1948 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Reuther, Walter, 1944-1948 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Reuther, Victor, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Research Action Committee, UAW (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Political Action Committee, 1944-1949 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Political Action Committee, 1944-1949 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Photographs (Box 3, Folder 3)
- New York State Industrial Union Council (Box 3, Folder 2)
- New York State Credit Union (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Cartoon Suggestions (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Agreements (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Agreements (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Agreements (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Agreements (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Bulletin Board Notices (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Addes, George, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Bulletin Board Notices (Box 4, Folder 8)
- General Motors Contract (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Central Foundry (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Delinquent Members (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Delinquent Members (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Delinquent Members (Box 4, Folder 13)
- General Motors Contract (Box 4, Folder 14)
- General Motors Contract (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Bulletin Board Notices (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Job Descriptions (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Job Descriptions (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Job Descriptions (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Harrison Radiator (communications) (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Harrison Radiator (communications) (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Harrison Radiator (communications) (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Harrison Radiator (communications) (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Harrison Radiator (communications) (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Harrison Radiator (communications) (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Harrison Radiator (communications) (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Harrison Radiator (communications) (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Minutes-Union Management Committee (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Membership lists (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Minutes-Union Management Committee (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Minutes-Union Management Committee (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Minutes-Union Management Committee (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Minutes-Union Management Committee (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Minutes-Union Management Committee (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Minutes-Union Management Committee (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Minutes-Union Management Committee (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Mandelare Case (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Minutes-Union Management Committee (Box 6, Folder 11)
- War Labor Board (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Pearson, Joseph, 1944-1948 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Pearson, Joseph, 1944-1948 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Reuther, Walter, 1946-1949 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Reuther, Walter, 1946-1949 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Reuther, Walter, 1946-1949 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Reuther, Walter, 1946-1949 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Skilled Trades Council (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Umpire Decisions, 1944-1948 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Thomas, R.J., 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Minutes-Union Management Committee (Box 6, Folder 10)
- National Labor Relations Board (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Membership Lists (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Agreements (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Agreements (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Agreements (Box 7, Folder 1)
- War Labor Board (Box 8, Folder 11)
- National Labor Relations Board (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Grievances (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Grievances (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Grievances (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Grievances (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Grievances (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 1)
- War Labor Board (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Agreements, 1947-1962 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Agreements, 1947-1962 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Agreements, 1947-1962 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Agreements, 1947-1962 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Harrison Radiator Union - Management Committee, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Harrison Radiator Union - Management Committee, 1942-1943 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Harrison Radiator Unit, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Harrison Radiator Unit, 1945-1946 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Local 686, 1958-1962 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Local 686, 1943-1945 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Mask Manufacturing vs. UAW, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Mask Manufacturing vs. UAW, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Mask Manufacturing vs. UAW, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- General Motors vs Harrison Radiator vs UAW, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- General Motors vs Harrison Radiator vs UAW, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- General Motors vs Harrison Radiator vs UAW, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- General Motors vs Harrison Radiator vs UAW, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- General Motors vs Harrison Radiator vs UAW, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Printed Material, ephemera and Voice of Labor, 1958-1977. For earlier issues see microfilm (Box 11)